Guide to the International Platform Association records, 1904-2001 MS2273
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Audiovisual materials, 1977-1999; 1990-1999; Series 7; 23 Linear Feet
  - The IPA 1994 Annual Convention, Series 7 (Box 83, Videocassette 4)
  - The IPA 1994 Annual Convention, Series 7 (Box 83, Videocassette 5)
  - The IPA 1994 Annual Convention, Series 7 (Box 83, Videocassette 6)
  - The IPA 1994 Annual Convention, Series 7 (Box 83, Videocassette 7)
  - The IPA 1994 Annual Convention, Series 7 (Box 83, Videocassette 8)
  - The IPA 1994 Annual Convention, Series 7 (Box 83, Videocassette 9)
  - The IPA 1994 Annual Convention, Series 7 (Box 83, Videocassette 10)
  - The IPA 1994 Annual Convention, Series 7 (Box 83, Videocassette 11)
  - The IPA 1994 Annual Convention, Series 7 (Box 83, Videocassette 12)
  - The IPA 1994 Annual Convention, Series 7 (Box 83, Videocassette 13)